https://www.util-locate.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicySCHEDULE A SERVICE ONLINE
Phone Name
Phone
Select Service You Need Select the Service You Need Utility Locating GPR Scanning Mapping Concrete Scanning Potholing CCTV Pipe Inspection
recaptcha0
Email
Call Now! 1(888)885-6228At Util-Locate, we are committed to protecting your privacy as a visitor to this Website and as our customer. To our visitors and to our customers, we offer this pledge:We will not sell, disseminate, disclose, trade, transmit, transfer, share, lease or rent any personally identifiable information to any third party not specifically authorized by you to receive your information except as we have disclosed to you in this Privacy Policy.Information CollectionWhen you send us email from this Website, you will provide us with certain personally identifiable information including your email address. At anytime, if you wish to no longer receive correspondences via email, please contact us via the address listed on our site under the “Contact” link.CookiesA cookie is a piece of data that is stored on a visitor’s hard drive while they are visiting this Website. We may utilize a short-lived form of cookie when you visit this site. At util-locate.com a cookie is only used to identify one unique visitor from another visitor during a particular session. A session is the period of active site-use while that unique visitor is linked to our server. We may use cookie technology during a session as a tool to carry forward your input information during the enrollment process. This enables the visitor to input their information once and have the information appear later during the enrollment process. No personally identifiable information is stored on the cookie. The cookie expires and is deleted from the visitor’s computer as soon as they close their browser.Third Party LinksThis Website may contain links to third party Websites that are not controlled by Util-Locate. These third party links are made available to you as a convenience and you agree to use these links at your own risk. Please be aware that the Util-Locate is not responsible for the content of third party Websites linked to the Util-Locate nor are we responsible for the privacy policy or practices of third party Websites linked to the Util-Locate Our Privacy Policy only applies to information we collect from you while you are at and while you are actively in a session with the Util-Locate If you should link to a third party Website from the Util-Locate, we strongly encourage you to review and become familiar with that Website’s privacy policy.Changes In Our Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without providing you with advance notice of our intent to make the changes.If you would like more information about our services and pricing in Southern California, call us Toll Free at +1(866)421-5325 or email us at info@util-locate.com. and we will be glad to answer any questions you may have.Leave a Reply Cancel replyYour email address will not be published. Required fields are marked *CommentName * Email * Website
Schedule Work
Contact Us
Common Ground AllianceNational Utility Locating Contractors AssociationUU & LL
×
